<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://starkey9000.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Runners</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/runners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/runners/</guid><description>The Course The course is mostly single track trail with a mix of open fields, dirt road and some paved road. The course features nearly 4,300 feet of climbing. There is a starting loop of 3 miles followed by two identical loops of 14 miles. There are 4 stream crossings that can be challenging depending on the water level – there is always the chance of getting wet feet.
HAT 50K on www.</description></item><item><title>Volunteers</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/volunteers/</guid><description>Calling all VOLUNTEERS… The volunteers make this race what it is! Please come and join us again, if you don’t have the time of your life, we’ll refund you in full.
We’re using UltraSignup again this year and the locations and shift times will be listed. We will need volunteers for Friday setup &amp;amp; packet pickup as well as Saturday race day registration, course marshals, aid station support, and trail sweeps.</description></item><item><title>Spectators</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/spectators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/spectators/</guid><description>There are 2 great viewing spots on the HAT run course to catch your runner multiple times.
Start / Finish and Upper Aid Station Steppingstone Museum 461 Quaker Bottom Road
Lower Aid Deer Creek Picnic Area 948 Stafford Road
The route between the 2 aid stations will be marked on race day with purple ‘pie-plates’.
Please drive carefully as you will cross the course multiple times along the way. Please do not stop on the road, except for the safety of runners.</description></item><item><title>Race Rules</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/race-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/race-rules/</guid><description>Absolutely NO Transferring of bib numbers. Registered runners only! This is critical to the safe tracking of all participants and the future of this event. If you are caught transferring or selling your bib, using a pacer or running as a bandit, you will be barred from future events.
Time Constraints will be STRICTLY enforced. These are not suggestions and are no longer up to the discretion of event staff or participants.</description></item><item><title>Race details now available on UltraSignup</title><link>https://starkey9000.github.io/news-and-updates/first-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starkey9000.github.io/news-and-updates/first-post/</guid><description>33rd Annual HAT 50K race details now available on ultrasignup.com. Registration opens November 25th, 2022 at 12:00PM EST.</description></item></channel></rss>