<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</title><link>https://hatrun.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on HAT RUN 50K</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hatrun.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Runners</title><link>https://hatrun.com/runners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hatrun.com/runners/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-course"&gt;The Course&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The HAT Run is held on the trails of Susquehanna State Park. The course is mostly single track trail with a mix of open fields, dirt road and some paved road. The course features nearly 4,300 feet of climbing. There is a starting loop of 3 miles followed by two identical loops of 14 miles. There are 4 stream crossings that can be challenging depending on the water level – there is always the chance of getting wet feet.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Volunteers</title><link>https://hatrun.com/volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hatrun.com/volunteers/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="calling-all-volunteers"&gt;Calling all VOLUNTEERS…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The volunteers make this race what it is! Please come and join us again. If you don’t have the time of your life, we’ll refund you in full. We use &lt;a href=https://ultrasignup.com/register.aspx?eid&amp;#61;1124 target="_blank"&gt;UltraSignup&lt;/a&gt; to register volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below the map are general instructions and information for all volunteers, and task-specific details you may find helpful in preparation for your big day. The captain of your assigned area will contact you in advance of race day with further information and to answer questions you may have. If you are under 18, parental approval is required on the Ultra Sign Up registration form.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Spectators</title><link>https://hatrun.com/spectators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hatrun.com/spectators/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;There are 2 great viewing spots on the HAT run course to catch your runner multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start / Finish and Upper Aid Station
Steppingstone Museum
461 Quaker Bottom Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lower Aid
Deer Creek Picnic Area
948 Stafford Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The route between the 2 aid stations will be marked on race day with purple ‘pie-plates’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please drive carefully as you will cross the course multiple times along the way. Please do not stop on the road, except for the safety of runners.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Race Rules</title><link>https://hatrun.com/race-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hatrun.com/race-rules/</guid><description>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Absolutely NO Transferring of bib numbers. Registered runners only! This is critical to the safe tracking of all participants and the future of this event. If you are caught transferring or selling your bib, using a pacer or running as a bandit, you will be barred from future events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time Constraints will be STRICTLY enforced. These are not suggestions and are no longer up to the discretion of event staff or participants. A runner MUST LEAVE an aid station ahead of cut off times. If you do not make a cut off time, please hand bib number to course marshall. The aid station captain will see that you have a ride back to race HQ. Anyone who finishes the race after 9:00 hours or 5:30 PM will be listed on the official finish with No Time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>